Kostadis Roussos: Are you fucking kidding me?
Kostadis Roussos: Hello.
Kostadis Roussos: Can you hear me?
Nikhil: Yes, I can hear you. Can you hear.
Kostadis Roussos: Of course I can. Yes, of course.
Kostadis Roussos: Seem.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Open up.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll 20.
Kostadis Roussos: You look good.
Kostadis Roussos: You must be hot.
Nikhil: Super hot, and I'll tell you something else.
Nikhil: The central AC controls…
Kostadis Roussos: are with the house owner. So.
Nikhil: Set the temperature, and locked up that box.
Nikhil: So I don't even have the, you know, ability to control the temperature.
Nikhil: And each room has a fan, so I just turned on my fan. It's still hot.
Kostadis Roussos: dude that's like cruel is he allowed to do that? yes he is.
Nikhil: So, lot of the, you know, house owners who rent out houses like this, they do that in San Jose and, you know, in the Bay Area.
Kostadis Roussos: Really?
Nikhil: Yep.
Nikhil: I've seen it at a couple of my friends' houses, like, before COVID.
Kostadis Roussos: 7 years ago.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. And they were renting…
Kostadis Roussos: That's really sucks.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I know. So I have a space heater in my room.
Nikhil: For winters because I cannot stand cold at all, so.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, me too.
Nikhil: It's really hot… it gets really cold in the winters, and I don't have the temperature control.
Kostadis Roussos: Do I have a space?
Nikhil: It's beautiful.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, let's see. Okay, so do you remember what happened last time?
Kostadis Roussos: Feel free to send. Okay. No, no, no, I'll tell you, let me tell you.
Nikhil: So, we went to that, cave, manor, and we found a…
Kostadis Roussos: Secret route and there was a cave.
Nikhil: And we went inside the coattails of.
Kostadis Roussos: Exactly.
Nikhil: Playing, like, mind games, like, you can control your mind and stuff.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I just want to remember what it said last so I don't forget.
Nikhil: I'm glad I remembered my memory.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, that's very impressive
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, that is true. All right. So let's see.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So yes, so you entered here and sat… the creature… the creature, what does the creature do? The creature speaks, reveals… revealed something about Pip.
Kostadis Roussos: And what did he reveal?
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see the recording he revealed. Let me see if I can pull this up.
Kostadis Roussos: He revealed that…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, I need to bring up my… Editor.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, he reveals that… He's, he revealed that…
Kostadis Roussos: Pip had recently won a strange blackstone shard in a dice game near Neverwinter Night Darks, then sold it to a peddler heading down toward Phandalin. Since then, Pip has dreamed of a broken blackstone beneath the earth and heard whispers saying his name.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip wants to find the peddler, buy or steal the shard back, and figure out why it is haunting him.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, so, is the creature, like…
Nikhil: Talking out loud, all of this.
Kostadis Roussos: I think it's a mind… I think it speaks… I think it's a mind creature. So it's only talking to people, or no? No, no, it's talking to all of you.
Nikhil: Can all of us hear this part?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes!
Kostadis Roussos: And.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, all of you can hear it, but the only person who can understand it is Sister Mela.
Kostadis Roussos: Since none of you speak Undercommon. She quickly translates.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. The creature then explains, "I am hungry."
Kostadis Roussos: And, and offers, offers to let you go if you're just willing to sacrifice one of your own.
Nikhil: That's why we have this great brand.
Kostadis Roussos: You're like, okay, you're gonna like toss him to the wolves?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I'm gonna…
Nikhil: Of course, I mean, I'll try to negotiate with the creature, like.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, we'll give you one of…
Nikhil: One of us, as we sacr… we'll sacrifice one of us, but what do we get in.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. I'm gonna, then one is going to talk to the creature, like, or maybe…
Nikhil: Tell Sister Naila to convey this thing, like, transmit this to the.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I'm blue, just give me a second,
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you're gonna try to convince… you're gonna have Sister Melee con… so… so… the creature… the creature looks at you and goes.
Kostadis Roussos: Looks at you, and it kind of licks its lips.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, it's a very… and as it licks its lips, you realize that it's got fangs that are going out of style.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh.
Nikhil: -H.
Kostadis Roussos: Just a question.
Nikhil: So is the creature loose, or is it, chained to.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, roll an investigation check.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll for everyone.
Kostadis Roussos: What's.
Nikhil: Yeah, 16.
Kostadis Roussos: Relax.
Nikhil: I think it's RD20.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you notice a dead goblin.
Kostadis Roussos: But it's kind of interesting.
Kostadis Roussos: These goblins have elongated skulls and are dressed in filthy haphazard rags.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So, the…
Nikhil: I'm gonna ask…
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, I can' Hold on, no, it's not you All right, speak.
Nikhil: Can you hear me.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I can, I can, I can.
Nikhil: Okay, so, I'm gonna…
Nikhil: Talk to the red brand and ask, like, what is this feature, why is it allocated?
Kostadis Roussos: Why, why does it have the, the, the, the, the, oh, you're talking to them, he's going, I'm not talking to you, you're gonna.
Nikhil: No, Ted, you know, we need to know, like, what… if you tell us, what… how to get out of… get past the situation, I'll… you'll be saved.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, I don't know how to get past the situation. I told you, man, somebody came down here, and came down to this lower area, and never came back. And there was, like, rumors about why he never came back.
Nikhil: Is this one of your guys? The guy who's dead?
Kostadis Roussos: No. He says, I've never… he looks at it and goes, I've never seen any goblin that.
Nikhil: And is the creature chained? So this question is to you. So is the creature chained or is it like roaming freely there?
Kostadis Roussos: With the, the, the, the creature with the, the claw, the teeth.
Nikhil: Yes, the mind creation.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh yeah he's he's he's like kind of like trying to figure out what you guys are gonna what you guys are gonna do.
Nikhil: Is it chained, or no?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, he's not changed blockchain, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: He is absolutely not chained.
Nikhil: So, yeah, like I said, I'm gonna try to negotiate with the preacher that will sacrifice one of us, and
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: What are you gonna get in return?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, I'll only eat one of you.
Kostadis Roussos: Sure, but what…
Nikhil: Can we do…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: You can continue to explore this area, and I don't have to tell you, I don't, and I won't kill you.
Nikhil: How do we trust you?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes… I like living, and why would I kill you if I've been fed?
Nikhil: It seems like a nice creature.
Nikhil: Cool, okay then, we'll sacrifice the red brand.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, the red brand? Is that your plan? So you're gonna turn on him? Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Give me a second now. Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, you're gonna sacrifice the red brand. Okay, the red brand,
Kostadis Roussos: What is the red brand new?
Kostadis Roussos: What, does the Red Dad do?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so first of all, the Red Brand does not just sort of like take it like, he doesn't take it.
Kostadis Roussos: That's what I'm looking
Kostadis Roussos: If you want to hear, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Here's the audio. I put the link into the audio.
Kostadis Roussos: If you want to hear creepy audio.
Nikhil: Yes, opening.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: The creature… Okay, so, I mean…
Kostadis Roussos: Your intuition is the creature isn't going to, freely negotiate.
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Nikhil: What do you mean by that?
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry. When I said freely negotiate, I misspoke.
Kostadis Roussos: What, your goal is… yeah, okay, so you wanna give… you're gonna give up Rondar, right? Okay. When Rondar hears that, he decides to bolt. And starts screaming.
Nikhil: Okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: This way.
Nikhil: I can't hear the sound.
Kostadis Roussos: You can't? If you click on that link.
Nikhil: I, I did, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: And you make sure you've turned on your audio volume for it. You don't have it.
Nikhil: I do, yes, I mean, volume is on because I can hear you.
Nikhil: That's because.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I mean, make sure that the vault, it's going through, make sure you've got the webpage, it's not muted accident.
Nikhil: It's not. Sound is automatic and default.
Nikhil: Preset the colours.
Kostadis Roussos: Could you share your screen with that web page on?
Kostadis Roussos: It's Christm.
Nikhil: Okay.
Nikhil: You've seen,
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, show me the audio. The audio's coming, it's just not popping, it's not going to your, click start.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, there's audio coming, because that's what you can tell from over.
Nikhil: let me switch my monitor.
Kostadis Roussos: or…
Nikhil: browser, because it's…
Nikhil: Let me try it on a different person.
Nikhil: This landscape is not supported in Safari.
Nikhil: I'm going to switch to a different monitor.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: You don't see the boxes in my room because I moved the table. Dude, I'm not a fool. I know you hid them. It's okay.
Nikhil: No, no, the boxes are still there.
Kostadis Roussos: I know, you hid them from me, you were very careful to make sure that I would not lecture you about the boxes again.
Nikhil: No, I changed my room orientation, I moved the table to the window side, and bed to the center.
Kostadis Roussos: To get more things.
Kostadis Roussos: Bye-bye That's fine.
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Cool.
Kostadis Roussos: Tell me when you're ready.
Nikhil: I'm ready, but I cannot hear this
Nikhil: Everyone'.
Kostadis Roussos: Cannot hear it? That's okay.
Kostadis Roussos: It's definitely playing on your computer.
Kostadis Roussos: The only other thing I would say is you may be disabled. Anyway, let's deal with it some other time, shall we?
Nikhil: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I might be able to, I might be able to do it differently.
Kostadis Roussos: You may be able, maybe you hear it now.
Kostadis Roussos: through my speaker.
Kostadis Roussos: Here, just do this.
Nikhil: penguin.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see, did you hear, let me just.
Audio shared by Kostadis Roussos: Thank you.
Audio shared by Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: You heard that? Yes. Okay, cool.
Nikhil: So I can.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, I'm sharing my computer audio. That'll work. All right. Awesome.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so the Gnothic you again.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, okay.
Audio shared by Kostadis Roussos: Shit.
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And so Rondar… Rondar decides he's had enough. He's gonna run. Roll for initiative.
Nikhil: Gonna run.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, dude! You just said I'm gonna feed him to the Nothic! And he's not gonna sit there! He screams, help! And he runs!
Kostadis Roussos: But, you know… Your master quiet plan did not quite work.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Meanwhile, Pip's kinda like, dude, you're a cold bastard!
Kostadis Roussos: All right, let's roll for initiative.
Nikhil: Yes, once again.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Perfect. Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Mmhm.
Kostadis Roussos: Or, sorry, that's okay, so, 10…
Nikhil: Okay, my initiative is…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. All right. And
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So.
Kostadis Roussos: 3D20. Let me just roll for initiative for the three, the three Los Tres, Los Tros Amigos.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so pip.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh my God.
Kostadis Roussos: The wall turns clear. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So, pip, turn.
Kostadis Roussos: is a 16.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, who's next?
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Mela.
Kostadis Roussos: Turn is a 10. Sorry, Vera is a 19.
Kostadis Roussos: Alvera, where is she?
Kostadis Roussos: Vera. Vera's over here.
Kostadis Roussos: And then, Sister Mela.
Kostadis Roussos: And turn is a 10. What was yours?
Kostadis Roussos: 15? Sorry, 30?
Nikhil: 13, 1, 3.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, 13.
Kostadis Roussos: And, rondar.
Kostadis Roussos: 7.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, Pip, you're up first. Okay, Pip's up.
Kostadis Roussos: This pip do.
Kostadis Roussos: What does Pip do?
Kostadis Roussos: So this creature's clearly gonna come after you, he's started shouting, he's decided that the, but…
Kostadis Roussos: The good news is that anybody who's out here probably thinks that the person who's about who's screaming help is screaming help because of the monster.
Kostadis Roussos: Not that he's actually trying to be saved, right? And so, from your perspective, so Pip does… Pip realizes that and says.
Kostadis Roussos: I wonder what to do next so Pip will try to knock Prandar prone Let me just do this.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, shuck, that's what I' No, that's not it. Okay And… So… And I'm knocking someone down.
Kostadis Roussos: Shot? Not a headshot.
Kostadis Roussos: Introduction.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, hold on. I need to figure out how to do this.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so he's gonna try to knock him prone.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, 8 plus your strong bond, okay, so that's 15, 13, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so he's going to try to knock him prone.
Kostadis Roussos: What does he do? His strength is plus 2, his proficiency is 12, right?
Kostadis Roussos: It's not too bad. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So… Tries to knock him prone so he doesn't run away.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so I guess he's going to do a dexterity. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: all right that did not succeed okay Xenophon, you're up.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip steps over here. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Zenimon.
Kostadis Roussos: You're up.
Kostadis Roussos: You can see the map, right?
Nikhil: Yes, I can see. I'm going to move.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Oh.
Nikhil: do the…
Kostadis Roussos: Remember, you can either sap first or nick first.
Nikhil: I know, I know, I'll do the neck so that I can, you know, hit and move back.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: That is a miss. All right, that was a natural one. All right, next tech.
Kostadis Roussos: But you get an advantage on your second attack. No, you don't. You get roll again.
Nikhil: Same scimitar, or should I…
Kostadis Roussos: The other, the other weapon.
Kostadis Roussos: Short sword or dagger, I don't know which one
Kostadis Roussos: alright, click on the roll damages
Kostadis Roussos: 12 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Oops.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, he's down to four.
Kostadis Roussos: No, he's down to, he's down to 4 hit points, he's down to 4 hit points, not 8 down, he's down 4.
Nikhil: Okay, I'm gonna move back.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Umm, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: We're gonna move back.
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Mela.
Kostadis Roussos: Umm.
Kostadis Roussos: looks at Rondar and says, What does she say?
Kostadis Roussos: What does Mela do?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Sister Mela decides that,
Kostadis Roussos: You know, this guy is a crook, a criminal, a thief, and a scoundrel, and, you know, quite frankly, he's not a good person. And as far as she's concerned, that means that, you know, she's done with him.
Kostadis Roussos: And she goes, it's nothing personal, you see, nothing personal.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, you can't expect me to not think it's personal when you're about to kill me!
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, yeah, I could see how you could see it that way, but I don'
Kostadis Roussos: So she strikes with her dagger.
Kostadis Roussos: Going up with her mace, hits, and kills him. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: The Nothic, the Nothic, says, what does he say?
Kostadis Roussos: The Gnostic is pleased.
Kostadis Roussos: He is very pleased.
Nikhil: Is it gonna grant us any wishes?
Audio shared by Kostadis Roussos: Does it come back forward because it's a pain?
Kostadis Roussos: What'd you say?
Nikhil: Is it gonna grant us any wishes, because it's a mind creature?
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's not. It's gonna grant you the right to not die.
Kostadis Roussos: He comes over here, and he drags the body over there.
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so are you guys gonna, are you gonna just try to fight him or are you gonna move on?
Nikhil: Quite the creature.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, I'm like, yes, I mean, he's eating, he's gone, he's taken R.
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip turns to you, Zonova, and says, where do we go next?
Nikhil: So, we try to enter the manor.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. You're, you're in the manor, right? You're in the basement of the manor, right? Yes. So we try to
Kostadis Roussos: I don't.
Nikhil: Is there anything closing this part? Like, we need to get there and…
Kostadis Roussos: You know, shut the door behind us for a little bit.
Nikhil: I'll take the first That's the plan.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you're currently in the Red Brands, hideout to go, like, defeat the Red Brands and see who the boss is, right?
Kostadis Roussos: That's… if you recall, that was… so you're trying to find out who's the boss, and so there's a passageway to the east and a passageway to the west. Which way would you like to
Kostadis Roussos: You've…
Nikhil: You still this one?
Nikhil: To my left.
Kostadis Roussos: we, always we, we east that is left to your left would be west.
Nikhil: Okay, oh, you said V, that's an acronym, okay. Left is West.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Nikhil: East is right.
Nikhil: Well, I mean, we can definitely ask Sinotic,
Kostadis Roussos: No, the Nothic's not interested in talking to you.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll take
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, your, your, as Sister Mila says, Xenobon, we probably want to get there before he decides he wants to eat more.
Nikhil: Okay, so… so I would want to go to the West.
Kostadis Roussos: The west?
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Works. Yeah, I see some stuff. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: So, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Remember this, this guy, the dead goblin?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so you notice he's got an elongated skull.
Nikhil: Correct, yes, yes, is there anything else?
Kostadis Roussos: No. And no treasure.
Nikhil: Only three characters, like Vera is missing.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: Vera is missing?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, she was over here. She's here.
Nikhil: Okay, cool.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay, so Zenon, let me just get the, let me just get this.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: You see a doorway over here.
Kostadis Roussos: What would you like to do at the, do you wanna listen at the door or how do you want, how do you wanna take that?
Kostadis Roussos: Listen at the door? Alright, roll your percep- what's your passive perce.
Nikhil: Perception.
Nikhil: It's plus 2.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: No, it should… 12. If you see on your character sheet, it should… there should be a 12. There should be a 12, and there should be a passive perception.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you hear creature, you hear various creatures in the door.
Nikhil: Wait, what? Do I hear creatures?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, on the other side of the door. Roll your investigation or insight to see whether you can figure out what kind of creatures.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see.
Nikhil: So, it is plus zero, or it's the investigation plus code, and I will be investigating.
Nikhil: 16.
Kostadis Roussos: You rolled a 16? All right. You hear there's several bugbears in that room. They're talking and they seem to be laughing. You also hear the goblin.
Nikhil: Okay, I see two doors on the map. One is behind me, one is in front of me.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, that's right. So to the south is where you heard the, Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll just write this.
Nikhil: Are they… can I go to the other door next door, or…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you can, absolutely. Absolutely.
Nikhil: Yeah, okay, I'm gonna go on to the other side of the door, and
Nikhil: I think the perception and investigation, same process, I think. So, do I need to roll an investigation?
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll a perception, yeah? Oh, your passive perception is a 12. Alright, roll an investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: That's true All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okey-dokey. You hear, there… whereas in the other room there were bugbears, this one you can hear what are clearly, humans laughing.
Kostadis Roussos: and playing some kind of gambling game.
Nikhil: So bugbears, in my opinion, seem to be more dangerous than the humans, so I'll try to go on to the north side, north shore.
Kostadis Roussos: all right
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you're gonna open the door? Now, let's… so, Sister Mela, Pip, Vera says, so what's the plan, boss? Just as you're about to open the door.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip says, boss, you know that other door? They might come out from that other door. What are we going to do if we're kind of trapped between the two groups?
Nikhil: Just to make sure both the doors are locked.
Kostadis Roussos: No, not really. They're closed. They're not locked.
Nikhil: I can just barge into any one of them, right? So…
Nikhil: Okay, so here's the plan, Vera.
Kostadis Roussos: We will…
Nikhil: All four of us, I kick the door open, and we all get in and close the door behind us.
Nikhil: And, see what the humans are doing.
Nikhil: And always be prepared to attack.
Nikhil: And try to, you know, we have the element of surprise, so…
Nikhil: Try to… we are four of us, and try to get to four humans, and… You know…
Kostadis Roussos: Put them at, squad. Put the squad to the next.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, all right.
Nikhil: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you're trying to try to surprise them, right?
Nikhil: Prize attack, it's.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, hold on, alright, so, okay, so, alright, so you're gonna try to burst into the room and try to surprise them. Okay, roll
Kostadis Roussos: Stealth, I guess. Yes. All right, everybody roll your stealth.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: That was not very good stealth, buddy.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: But I like it.
Nikhil: Okay, enough.
Kostadis Roussos: That might have been enough, given these guys' passive perception. Yep, you met… you… all of you managed… you managed to surprise the group.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. The door opens. You see these four bandits. Let me just describe, read to you what you see.
Nikhil: Oh, just 4 of them. 4 of them. Okay, cool. We'll get one.
Kostadis Roussos: right
Kostadis Roussos: Several worn tables and chairs are scattered around this large room. Wooden benches are drawn up against the walls, decorated with brown and red draperies, and several ale kegs are propped and tapped… propped up and tapped.
Kostadis Roussos: Four tough-looking human warriors wearing scarlet cloaks are gathered around one of the tables. A stack of coins and trinkets is heaped upon the table between them.
Kostadis Roussos: all right you're you're you've decided you're gonna go for the kill.
Nikhil: Ish.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes?
Nikhil: I mean, not for the kill, like,
Nikhil: Like I described, like, we want to… I want to hold each one of them,
Nikhil: What do you say? As a prisoner, and then talk to them.
Kostadis Roussos: Before they show up.
Nikhil: Does that work, or…
Nikhil: Are they too strong for me to do that?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, Pip says, boss, there's like four fighters there and two of us.
Nikhil: Okay, okay, I'll change the plan. So, we'll fight them, and then we'll get them to their knees, down to their knees, and then maybe talk before we can…
Kostadis Roussos: Vera says, I think that plan works best if you coordinate it with the sign… with, like… and she starts going off on her crazy talk again.
Nikhil: Yeah, yeah. You picked the strongest one, Vera.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Oh, she's very happy. She's like, oh, thank you. All right. Okay, Xenavon, what's your initiative?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And, pip.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: So,
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. What did you get for initiative?
Kostadis Roussos: Eight. Eight.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know, 17.
Kostadis Roussos: Mila is four. It's necessary. It's two.
Kostadis Roussos: And.
Kostadis Roussos: Vera is eight.
Kostadis Roussos: all right Pip goes first so
Kostadis Roussos: Pick charges in, and Wax attempts to… no, so that's Mila. Pick charges in… And
Kostadis Roussos: Bandits sort of look at him, he looks at them, and he says.
Kostadis Roussos: Never did like the crooked kind, it never did like the crooked kind.
Kostadis Roussos: And he rolls to hit.
Nikhil: It was a heroic entry, quite.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, Pip definitely did the heroic entry. He's got to say, what does he get up to a hit?
Kostadis Roussos: Plus four to hit. I think that's enough to hit this guy.
Kostadis Roussos: yes it is all right so he takes
Kostadis Roussos: How much do they take? T-t-takes?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. They take 6 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty,
Nikhil: Paper tags is one of them.
Kostadis Roussos: yeah yeah he attacks this one here can you see his you should be able to see his here.
Nikhil: The guy with the beard or the red back?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, here, you should now see him.
Nikhil: Bandit.
Kostadis Roussos: And you should now see him with less hit points.
Nikhil: Oh, wow. I love this bar. This is really healthy.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Bye.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Vera.
Kostadis Roussos: Comes over here… And, alright, we'll cast Magic Missile.
Kostadis Roussos: You could have done better Vera.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: This red brand here.
Kostadis Roussos: Takes two points of damage. All right, Xenophon, you're up.
Nikhil: And.
Nikhil: And use my wigs.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: What is it? Command?
Kostadis Roussos: You just roll, and then on the second attack, you get advantage.
Kostadis Roussos: That's true.
Kostadis Roussos: From Japanese.
Kostadis Roussos: You did 12 points of damage? Against whom? No, you missed!
Nikhil: Wait, no Very, very nice.
Kostadis Roussos: You rolled a… you rolled a 10.
Nikhil: You rolled a 10. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Now you've got advantage on your second attack. Who do you want to attack?
Nikhil: The red brand of you?
Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Go for it.
Nikhil: 3.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, that's… that one's a hit, or a damage?
Nikhil: I'm just.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, he's down to, the bandit is down to, 3 hit points.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Mela.
Kostadis Roussos: What does she do?
Nikhil: I'm gonna be.
Kostadis Roussos: But.
Nikhil: Just create space for them.
Kostadis Roussos: If you move back, you're gonna cause… you're gonna create an attack of opportunity. She doesn't need you to move back.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: She can, walk around you.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, she's gonna whack this guy.
Kostadis Roussos: And she kills him.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: Question? No.
Nikhil: Can they attack even if they have, like, one hit point left?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, they can attack. You're magically healed until your last breath. Alright, Pip.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so it's Pip's turn, and Pip is going to attack the rem.
Nikhil: Vera? Vera?
Nikhil: We're still outside.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, she's over here so she can cast spells, she doesn't.
Nikhil: Okay, but her turn did not appear yet.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, she did. She cast Magic M.
Nikhil: Magic wizard? Okay, okay, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Pip.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so Pip will attack… The red brand muffin.
Kostadis Roussos: That you will do.
Nikhil: In the back, or…
Kostadis Roussos: Another one right in front, and he will miss spectacularly. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, that's bread brand rough in.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: comes rushing at Sister Mela and shouts really loudly.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Screaming for the other bugbears to come help her.
Kostadis Roussos: And, rolls to attack Sister Mela, and misses.
Kostadis Roussos: all right the other red brand muffian Thwacks I don't know Waxed xenophon.
Nikhil: Sorry, I wanted.
Kostadis Roussos: 9 points of damage. No, no, no damage. He misses you entirely. Alright, Vera steps forward.
Kostadis Roussos: And cast a Firebolt.
Kostadis Roussos: And Mrs. Xenophon, you're up Why is everyone missing?
Kostadis Roussos: It's the luck of the draw.
Nikhil: I'll do the short VEX again, so…
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: I did not waste this time, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, put down.
Nikhil: I guess.
Nikhil: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on. So, you don't need your sneak… you can use your sneak attack on… well, you can't, because you used it… you… you… yeah. Okay. This guy… is dead.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright!
Kostadis Roussos: You can try to attack the other red brand.
Nikhil: I was thinking, can I attack the red brand with the other red brand with this
Nikhil: First attack and then second one to the dead guy.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so… well, you don't know if you're gonna hit the dead guy, and you don't get advantage on the second attack, because the VEX only applies to somebody who hit.
Nikhil: No, it's.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Scroll again.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Hit.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Nikhil: It's 12 points.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, only, I guess, yeah, alright, so you did 4 points, you killed them with 4 points, you'll use a sneak attack here, you do 12 points of damage. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Read the part on the.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh yeah, sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: What does the bandit do?
Kostadis Roussos: Found it.
Kostadis Roussos: Comes this way.
Kostadis Roussos: Attacks Vera because he wants to get through her to get out of here
Kostadis Roussos: And he hits her for… 4 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Malef.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Sister Mela, why don't you roll to attack for her to attack? D20 plus 4, she's gonna hit with her
Kostadis Roussos: That is a miss.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on. I just realized something.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip has a special ability.
Kostadis Roussos: Umm…
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, hold on, so I imposes a disadvantage on that attack, so maybe she doesn't take. Oh, no, she, he would have still hit. Alright, so, Pip
Kostadis Roussos: We'll thrac… we'll try to… No, no, no, we'll attack the bandit.
Kostadis Roussos: Hits for.
Kostadis Roussos: 6 points of damage. Alright?
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, the red brand Moruffian.
Kostadis Roussos: We'll thwack, I guess.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Mela.
Kostadis Roussos: And misses. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Vera will use her second magic missile and hopefully do better this time.
Nikhil: So.
Kostadis Roussos: And kills them. Yeah, she, no, she uses two on the bandit and one on the red-brown, they're all dead.
Nikhil: That side, I think.
Kostadis Roussos: She was attacked. She, she, you could definitely feel that she, like, this was a, a sudden reaction. Now, the one thing you do know is that there is bugbears coming by and the door is still open. Do you want to close the door? Do you want to barricade it in? What would you like to do?
Nikhil: I want to close the door.
Kostadis Roussos: alright, door is closed.
Nikhil: Yes, and then,
Nikhil: No, I was hoping to get some information out of the bandits and the red brands.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, you might want to talk to Vera about not killing all the bat…
Nikhil: Maybe, yeah, I'll explore the room to see if I can get any…
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, but if you don't want Vera to kill people all the time, you probably need to talk to her and explain to her what you want.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So.
Nikhil: Hey, Vera, I was hoping that, you know, we could have some information from one of these guys.
Nikhil: But, looks like you just killed all the cubs, right?
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, they were about to kill me!
Nikhil: I get it, like, like, you know, you can just, you know, damage them but not kill them, like, so that we can talk to them.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so I have to run to the bathroom. Nikhil, I'm gonna run to the bathroom, I'll be back in 2 minutes
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Where are we? Are you still there?
Kostadis Roussos: Hey, all right.
Nikhil: How are you.
Kostadis Roussos: So Vera, Vera is, you know, she's, roll your persuasion.
Nikhil: So I shouldn'
Nikhil: 11 plus 30.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Vera is partially convinced. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: You look at the, treasure. So, since you killed,
Kostadis Roussos: Since you… since you managed to kill them all, you can seize their treasure. You find 75 copper pieces… okay, so let me just…
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just put this in the, Treasure, and I'm gonna put it in the Zoom, the…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. The Discord chat.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, and then… Divide by 4 is gonna be the simple rule.
Kostadis Roussos: So.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So 75 copper pieces, 55 silver pieces, so that divided by 4, so…
Kostadis Roussos: We can, well we can deal with it later. Alright?
Nikhil: I'll just put slash four.
Nikhil: Yeah, terrific.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, while you're digging that, you… one of the… the door op… the door on the other side opens…
Kostadis Roussos: And a bugbear… you hear a bugbear knocking on.
Nikhil: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: And shouting in a very husky, beg-berry, butt-berry voice, Everything okay in there?
Nikhil: Wait, hold on
Nikhil: Yes, I'll roll my deception and try to respond in one of the bandit or the red brand's voice.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: I don't know how their voice sounds, but I'll try.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, you, you can, I mean, you're, you're, you, you can, I mean, who knows.
Nikhil: I'll try to make it up. I'll try to be a bandit and say, It's all good.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay.
Nikhil: deception.
Nikhil: Yeah. Nice deception, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: That's a nice deception. The bugbear shrugs and goes and walks away.
Kostadis Roussos: You hear the door close behind him.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: So, we'll explore the room, so… Investigation? Sure.
Kostadis Roussos: You already did, there's nothing else, here. The one thing you do notice is that the red brands have purple… have these red,
Kostadis Roussos: Cloaks, you might want to take them to disguise yourself with them.
Nikhil: Oh, okay.
Nikhil: But there are only two cloaks, I suppose. Like, for the bandits, do they have cloaks as well?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, they all, actually all of them, they all, they all have,
Nikhil: Cool, so, I'll say to the team, guys, let's all pick up the cloaks and disgu.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll just put a little red dot to indicate that you're wearing the…
Nikhil: Red Books, Red Books.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. There's a door to the north.
Nikhil: Yes, I see that,
Nikhil: You guys wanna go into that door, or do you guys wanna go fight the red brands?
Kostadis Roussos: What do you mean? What do you mean the red brick?
Nikhil: Another advance, the bugbears.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip.
Nikhil: Some of us per talk yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip says, we don't have to fight the bugbears, we could probably box them in by putting some of these barrels in front of the door.
Nikhil: That's really smart of you. Okay, let's do that.
Kostadis Roussos: all right so you put some barrels in here all right.
Nikhil: Take these bottles and park the door.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: That's feral.
Kostadis Roussos: Perfect.
Kostadis Roussos: I will just draw something.
Kostadis Roussos: A barrel has been placed in front of the door.
Nikhil: Nice.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, I will assume you put more than one. Okay, so to the the north door over here.
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: You're all dressed in your cool, snazzy outfits.
Nikhil: Yes, I wanna, again, put my ear and…
Nikhil: Hear to the door and hear what's going on.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: It is, there is, there is nothing there.
Kostadis Roussos: Whatever, you hear nothing.
Kostadis Roussos: Other than, let me see if I can do this again.
Kostadis Roussos: Other than…
Kostadis Roussos: The Nothic is very happily digesting.
Nikhil: Oh, that's the sound of.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, did you open the door?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil: Let's open.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: The door is opened.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, there's another door on the other side.
Nikhil: Yep.
Nikhil: So it's… there's another door, right
Nikhil: After I open this door, like…
Kostadis Roussos: Right, yeah, there's a door right there. You can see it right in front. You.
Nikhil: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: You gonna try to listen to that at that door as well?
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, what's your… roll your… roll your insight.
Kostadis Roussos: Or investigation.
Nikhil: Roll the investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nikhil: 11.
Kostadis Roussos: You, you do not hear anything.
Nikhil: So it's a miss, or… it's a miss, or do I not hear anything after it?
Kostadis Roussos: when, you do not hear anything.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Mela says, have you tried cupping your hands? So she tries to help you. You can roll again.
Nikhil: 13.
Kostadis Roussos: Still nothing.
Nikhil: I mean, what's to my east? Is it, like, the st.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, it's the stairs, and through there you can definitely hear the Nothic.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Well, since we are…
Nikhil: Disguised and cloaked, so let's try to open the door and see what's gonna… what's happening.
Nikhil: We are anyway, like, blended in them when we started.
Nikhil: What do you say, guys.
Kostadis Roussos: They agree, so I'm assuming you open the door. I was looking to get, I was looking to.
Kostadis Roussos: To play the appropriate sounds.
Nikhil: I don't think so.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. This room appears to be a wizard's workshop.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, this appears to be a wizard's worksh Hold on.
Nikhil: What do we.
Kostadis Roussos: A large work table is set up with alembics, retorts, distillation coils, and other alchemical devices, all of them stewing and bubbling away. Bookshelves are crowded with sheaves of parchment and strange-looking tomes.
Nikhil: Hey, Vera, can you come over here? Looks like this is your playground.
Nikhil: Where are you.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: Looks like this is your playground. Why don't you come check this.
Kostadis Roussos: She's like, this is very cool.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll let's see what does she discover she rolls her Arcana she goes…
Kostadis Roussos: well, this is really interesting, but I'm not sure I know what it's all about. And she's, like, kind of like…
Kostadis Roussos: Touches, she's like, you know that, that, that person who goes into the, the jewelry shop and touches everything.
Nikhil: Kid in a candy store.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Do you find anything useful for Azvera? What are they trying to do here?
Kostadis Roussos: Be real.
Nikhil: Can you repeat that?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, Vera looks at this and goes, oh, this is interesting, and says that this apparatus is set up to brew a potion of vis's ability. Then she looks at the notes, but he hasn't been successful thus far. Sister Bela is perusing the books, and she notices one.
Kostadis Roussos: is, is written in Dwarvish. She picks it up. It's the journal of an adventurer named Urman. It describes the history of the Lost Mind of Phandelver and the Forge of the Spells.
Kostadis Roussos: In addition, Urmond records that a magic mace named Lightbringer was commissioned by the priests of Lathander, the gods of dawn, from the mages working with the gnomes and dwarves of the Fandilever Pact. The mace was lost when the wave echo caved and its mind vanished from history.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: There is a door to the north.
Nikhil: Can you pick up any of these portions or, you know?
Kostadis Roussos: This equipment, She… so, Vera looks at it and says.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, most of this rheumatoid… most of the stuff here has no value, but these 3 bottles do, and she points out to 3 bottles with rare reagents. Mercury, Dragon Bile, and Powdered Nightshade.
Kostadis Roussos: Each worth 25 gold pieces each.
Nikhil: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Loop.
Nikhil: So now there's a door to the east.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil: So, we'll open the door.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: You can open the door. Hold on, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: The walls of this bank chamber are covered with drapes of scarlet cloth.
Kostadis Roussos: The furnishings include a small writing desk with a matching chair, a comfortable-looking bed, and a wooden chest at the foot of the bed.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: You see a door to the north, which was clearly a secret door that somebody has clearly left.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so do you want to go chase the guy who went through the secret door or do you want to,
Kostadis Roussos: What do you want to do?
Nikhil: Oh, I wanna chase the guy through the secret door, yeah. Hey guys, looks like somebody just left and opened the door, like…
Kostadis Roussos: Come on.
Nikhil: That's how.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Uhhh… Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Nikhil: Looks like it's waiting for some share.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, yeah, I need to… give me a second, I need to do something.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's roll for initiative.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: It's a cold.
Kostadis Roussos: What'd you roll?
Nikhil: 4.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: That's strange, if now it is showing my name, then… okay, that's from the beyond.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so we'll put, I'll put pip disk 20 plus one.
Kostadis Roussos: This is plus two, so that pips plus two.
Kostadis Roussos: That's 14.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Mela is just a rod, D20.
Kostadis Roussos: That's a one.
Kostadis Roussos: Vera. Vera over here.
Kostadis Roussos: That is a 16.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, she's got the tent.
Kostadis Roussos: No, she had a 1.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so… Vera one two.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, here it is. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Kostadis Roussos: And… She sees.
Kostadis Roussos: What's this guy doing? Just make sure I have this correct.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, okay, so.
Kostadis Roussos: Here he goes.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Vera sees him, and says, Boss, do I kill him or not?
Nikhil: Wait, what's happening? Why…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, stairs…
Kostadis Roussos: So you can… she sees the bad guy, she shouts to you, do I kill him or not? No, no, you're… it's not your turn yet.
Nikhil: Oh, okay. Okay, I don't have, view of what's happening. No. Hold on, don't hurt him, but don't kill him yet. Try to stop him from running, like, shoot him with, like.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so she attacks him with his firebolt, and this time he does get hit.
Nikhil: Yeah, reservation.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, let's see.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty, so she does a Firebolt.
Kostadis Roussos: 5 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: No, it would help if I put it in the right layer. Alright. Okay, he takes 5 points of damage.
Nikhil: So.
Nikhil: Can I go?
Nikhil: Find the stairs and see what.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on. It's Pip's turn. You rolled very poorly on your initiative.
Kostadis Roussos: So pip goes one, two, three, four, five, six.
Kostadis Roussos: He, pip uses his Javelin.
Kostadis Roussos: and hits
Kostadis Roussos: What does he do?
Kostadis Roussos: Javelin, takes 5 more points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Can you put a bar on this? Oh yeah, sorry, sorry, yes.
Nikhil: Paris Levy.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so pip, all right, so what does this guy do?
Nikhil: OpenSpace.
Kostadis Roussos: You recognize him from the description, soldar gave you.
Nikhil: Ohh.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: He, like, teleports himself.
Kostadis Roussos: He's going to run this way.
Kostadis Roussos: And then.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. You have no idea what he's doing. Okay. Shouldn't be able to see him. All right. Xenomon
Kostadis Roussos: So,
Nikhil: But, stairs?
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, over here.
Kostadis Roussos: Here.
Nikhil: Maybe a little bit tight.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: Maybe a little to the side, not up here.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Okay.
Nikhil: Okay, I'm gonna… Before… one second, we'll go… Wow.
Nikhil: Yeah, I'll throw that in. Intimidation. So I'm gonna ask him.
Nikhil: Do you want to live, or do you want to die in our hands? Do you want to talk, or do you want to fight first.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: He… he… you… you hear him, like, very far away, as if he's, like, run 100 feet.
Kostadis Roussos: The last thing you hear is him shouting to the Nauthic.
Kostadis Roussos: I pay you to e-kill- to protect this entrance, not to feast on whatever bodies I presented to you!
Nikhil: No problem, Paul. Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, he… what happened… okay, so just to tell you what happened. He ran 30 feet, then he cast Teleport.
Nikhil: Oh, teleport.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, and so he… and he shouted to the Nothic to, like, stop eating the half… stop eating and to go fight whoever's chasing him.
Nikhil: So, he's, he's, like, 30 feet far from me.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it's like 60 feet away.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you have a short bow?
Nikhil: I have a short bow, yes. I'm gonna.
Kostadis Roussos: I was checking. Yeah, everything is, like, 5 feet.
Nikhil: And use the sharp tool.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: What's the range of a shortbow.
Nikhil: 80.
Kostadis Roussos: For… is it 80 and 160?
Nikhil: 80 and a 32.
Kostadis Roussos: You missed.
Kostadis Roussos: Nice try. All right, Sister Mela.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: What does she do?
Kostadis Roussos: What is Sacred Flame? Like, she'll try to see… What does Lots of stermela.
Kostadis Roussos: She will try Sacred Flame, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: And he makes a saving throw.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: he runs away.
Kostadis Roussos: The Nothic… comes this way and says, Do you have any more food?
Nikhil: Okay, so he escapes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, he escapes.
Nikhil: So, yes, yes, we have lots of tools for you.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Cheers.
Audio shared by Kostadis Roussos: What do I do?
Nikhil: So, so, just to, understand, like, from the secret passages going back into the…
Kostadis Roussos: The…
Nikhil: Nautics Place, like, where we entered from, the same.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm sorry, what was… Yeah, yeah, basically what you've done is you, you, you started this way.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: And, foreground.
Kostadis Roussos: You're gone.
Kostadis Roussos: We went, west, and then…
Kostadis Roussos: It should. Yeah, yeah. Got it.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Yeah, okay,
Kostadis Roussos: Don't forget, you have the 4 other bodies in there, and you can tell them to go eat.
Nikhil: I know that's why I said yes, we have more food.
Kostadis Roussos: You tell them where they are?
Nikhil: Yes, we try to walk out of the same place, and then we find them… we find the Nautic…
Kostadis Roussos: Words.
Nikhil: The room where the dead bodies are.
Kostadis Roussos: the Nothic goes over here alright what do you want to do next?
Kostadis Roussos: Do you want to go look whether he left anything behind in his room?
Nikhil: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, I wanna examine this table.
Kostadis Roussos: I thought we did, actually. No, you examined, you examined his, wizard's workshop.
Nikhil: Right, okay. So, I wanna go back and examine…
Kostadis Roussos: The table.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, it's a groom Right.
Kostadis Roussos: you can go back just go back just place it okay do it right here all right so what do we have in this wizard's room?
Nikhil: I'm disappoint.
Kostadis Roussos: Or you just…
Nikhil: Faster.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: The walls? Okay, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, various papers and notes are stacked on the desk, mostly consisting of Glastaff's written orders to apothecaries and alchemists in nearby settlements for more materials for his workshop. However, you also notice a letter sealed with a wax symbol in the shape of a spider.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so I just showed you what the letter says.
Kostadis Roussos: Water hybrid.
Nikhil: Spicy now.
Kostadis Roussos: Stream is here.
Nikhil: They could be working.
Kostadis Roussos: Next.
Nikhil: Capture them if you can.
Nikhil: In a few months.
Nikhil: But don't allow them to upset our plans, either. Any proven maps?
Nikhil: That position is delivered immediately.
Kostadis Roussos: So, county.
Kostadis Roussos: Yup.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nikhil: Mmhm.
Kostadis Roussos: If, just to, just to remind you.
Kostadis Roussos: The Spider was somebody you heard was the big boss of the… The goblins.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait.
Nikhil: Spider was a character that I was introduced to.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I believe so.
Nikhil: It is
Nikhil: Oh, yes, yes. A mysterious villain known as the Spider controlled the network of bandit gangs and dropped the bandit radio.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes. Follow the roxy tickers to their price.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nikhil: Let's get rid of that.
Kostadis Roussos: So, yeah, so the spider apparently, so somebody who, maybe the spider or somebody who really likes spider art sent him a note saying that you now have proof who Yarno really works for.
Kostadis Roussos: Y Right, which is… which may be valuable to,
Kostadis Roussos: To… what's his name? Sildar.
Kostadis Roussos: Sonar.
Nikhil: Find Gunter.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. You also know that,
Kostadis Roussos: Yarno was probably responsible for capturing Gundrun and Rockseeker.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: But… Do you want to keep exploring?
Nikhil: Wait, I'm just gonna paste this, letter from Spider.
Kostadis Roussos: It it should it should have it okay yeah.
Nikhil: I'm just making notes. Okay.
Nikhil: What do I want to explore?
Kostadis Roussos: All right, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, there's grabs and scrolls. Alright, so, inside, you do see an open chest where he was trying to… where there was a bunch of stuff there.
Kostadis Roussos: It contains a bunch of gold.
Kostadis Roussos: Contains a bunch of treasure.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Some more treasure.
Nikhil: Variety of What are Carnelians?
Kostadis Roussos: They're they're kind of gem.
Nikhil: Okay, and paradox are also…
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, hold on, this is like, I don't know what they look like, so let's, this is
Kostadis Roussos: Was it Peridot?
Nikhil: Very dumb, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: This is a Peridot.
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see that one now.
Kostadis Roussos: Carnelians.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, the thing I love, like, I think the thing I love about this is that, you know, this game requires you to be a gemstone expert.
Nikhil: They look like… carnelians look like red pebbles.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Copy image address.
Kostadis Roussos: And this is what, this is what carnelians look like.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. There is a, there is a, there, you, you, yeah, there are.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, in this chamber where you are, you, you can, you hear the Nothic, crunching his way through more cadavers.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me just describe to you what this room here looks like.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty. This area is the north end of a large natural cavern, but it has been finished with dressed stone black walls and a flagstone floor. Several barrels are stored against the walls here, along with empty crates, straw for packing hammers, pry bars, and nails.
Kostadis Roussos: The cavern continues for some distance to the south. You can make out several passageways, then open off the larger cavern and what looks like a deep pit or crevasse in the floor. You guys know what that looks like.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: It's not saying anything about secret doors.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Roll, okay. So roll a insight or investigation.
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: What'd you roll?
Kostadis Roussos: 14. You find a secret door.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you want to go?
Nikhil: Just to be clear, like, Black Staff teleported, or, like, you know.
Nikhil: Teleported info for… did he go through the secret door?
Kostadis Roussos: And he went through the south.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just, I'll just, I'll draw, tell you where he went.
Kostadis Roussos: Actually, it didn't go this way
Kostadis Roussos: He, he, the last you saw him was he went that way.
Nikhil: Okay, like, out of the tree.
Nikhil: From where we came. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Open the secret code.
Kostadis Roussos: You gonna open the door?
Kostadis Roussos: All right, go in.
Nikhil: I don't see it at all.
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's a locked door. That's a locked door.
Nikhil: Both of them are locked.
Kostadis Roussos: No, the door right across from you is locked, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just do something. As you open the secret door.
Nikhil: Should I click on it?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Nikhil: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: That's you opening a secret stone door.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so there's this… there's a door… there's a locked door to the east and a door to the south.
Nikhil: Yes, okay, so… What happens if I click on the locker?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you have to un- you have to unlock- you have to try to unlock it, so that's where you would have to roll a skill check, sleight.
Nikhil: Oh, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Wow, okay.
Nikhil: Okay, so my question was, like, you said the door was locked, but if I click it on the map, will it open and show me the map, or…
Kostadis Roussos: I don't think so, it shouldn.
Nikhil: Okay, yes, okay, nice, that's cool.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, okay, so you open the door. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know. Plum, plum, plum.
Nikhil: Can I go in? Okay.
Nikhil: This has…
Kostadis Roussos: Racks of weapons line the walls of this chamber, including spears, swords, crossbows, and bolts.
Kostadis Roussos: A dozen dirty red cloaks hang from the hooks by the door.
Kostadis Roussos: You notice that this, the, the red brands have ambition, you, so roll an insight or roll an insight check.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip! Alright, let's also roll for Pip's Insight. Roll for Pip'.
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. All right. Pip says, huh, that's a lot of weapons. Somebody's trying to build an army.
Nikhil: Interesting. Okay, let's all pick it up, guys.
Nikhil: Hmm, right here you don't.
Kostadis Roussos: So you're gonna try to pick up all the equipment? Alright. How about… carrying it all right now with you would be a bit challenging, but I'll assume that if you empty the dungeon, you can come pick it up. Or you can try to see if there's anything of particular value.
Nikhil: Okay,
Nikhil: Is there some… okay, let's… let's see what we can… what could be useful to us back and forward.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, so there's like… here, I'll just describe to you.
Kostadis Roussos: You're also just up.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nikhil: Welcome Maxwell Press PS6 Short Short Short.
Kostadis Roussos: If you're gonna pick up a weapon, you can pick up a weapon. Pip is going to pick up a crossbow.
Nikhil: Please.
Nikhil: Specialty.
Nikhil: Oh, I like the short sword. I'm gonna swap it with the short sword I have.
Kostadis Roussos: Why?
Nikhil: It has, like, semi-precious stones.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you want a prettier short start. Okay.
Nikhil: See that? Isn't that the point of like.
Nikhil: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, like, like, you know, I think that's cool. Yes. I think that.
Nikhil: Heroes on the short sword, you know, like, weapon, weapon acquired.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip says, well, if you're gonna get something pretty, he drops the crossbow that didn't have the semi-precious stones, and picks up one that has the semi-precious stones.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Mela rolls her eyes. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: There's a door to the south.
Kostadis Roussos: Senator Vaughn, are you gonna do the investigation thing again?
Nikhil: Oops, okay.
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Fifteen.
Nikhil: Was this door locked or open?
Kostadis Roussos: It was unlocked, you haven't opened it Alright, you hear nothing.
Nikhil: I wouldn't worry much, because we are all closed and disguised, so I'll open that.
Kostadis Roussos: Gonna open the door?
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Three large stone sarcophagi stand with this desolate crypt.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, step inside.
Nikhil: Shit, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And six skeletons and rusty mail are propped against the walls as if guarding the place.
Kostadis Roussos: False columns along the walls are carved in the image of spreading oak trees. The double door in the southeast corner is sheathed in tarnished plates.
Kostadis Roussos: Just start back.
Nikhil: So, first…
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: No, this just got dark so fast, that escalated quickly.
Kostadis Roussos: What do you mean? Well, they're not moving, so these are, like, these 6 skeletons, and they're not.
Nikhil: No, no, no, what I felt was, as soon as I opened the door, I saw those 3 ghost-like people, and I was scared.
Nikhil: I bet they're not moving.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: It actually sent shivers down my spine.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, good! Good, good, good, good! I'm glad to hear.
Nikhil: Okay, okay.
Nikhil: Interesting.
Nikhil: Detect purpose.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Mela.
Kostadis Roussos: Comes over there, and she rolls her religion, her arcana check. What is it? Religion?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, I'm gonna give her an arcana. Ugh, she detect
Kostadis Roussos: Vera also rolls an Arcana check, and says, I think they're animated skeletons.
Nikhil: Animated?
Nikhil: What do you mean?
Kostadis Roussos: Well.
Kostadis Roussos: If we walk in there or do something, they might suddenly attack us, so we just better be careful.
Nikhil: Oh, fuck, okay.
Nikhil: Quickly.
Nikhil: Whatever I go plan… A tricky thing compared to a tricky decision.
Kostadis Roussos: So, where do you want to go? There's the three sarcophaguses, the door to the north, and the door to the south. The door to the northeast, and the door to the southeast, and we will stop.
Nikhil: You just said, that if I make a move, if I move forward, these skeletons.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, no, she is… she goes, I don't know. She goes… she says, well, they might. I mean, usually when the skeletons are here to attack you right on sight, but these ones haven't moved, so I don't know.
Nikhil: Okay.
Nikhil: I'm scared. Is there a scare role? Can I roll a scare or something?
Nikhil: Okay, sure.
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip says, Boss, do you want me to go in front.
Nikhil: I don't wanna… I don't want to appear scared.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nikhil: What's a history rule?
Nikhil: Like, can I get to know the history of something or something?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, use your history. Roll a history check.
Kostadis Roussos: What'd you roll?
Nikhil: Right.
Nikhil: 18.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, no, you rolled fantastic. This used to be the elders… this used to be the set… the… the… the… where the elders…
Kostadis Roussos: What is it? A Tresander Crypt.
Kostadis Roussos: to send our crypts.
Kostadis Roussos: This is where the the old family.
Kostadis Roussos: The elders of the family used to be buried here.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So… What are we gonna do?
Nikhil: That's relieving to know.
Nikhil: Meaning.
Nikhil: It's harmless, and then, channel page overload.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, there's…
Nikhil: One door to the northeast, and two doors to the southeast.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil: So, I'm gonna open the door in the northeast.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm gonna go over here. Okay, the minute you step over here, the skeletons animate, reroll for initiative, and we stop.
Nikhil: Sure.
Nikhil: Oh, no.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: No, that's bad.
Nikhil: Oh, fuck, okay. I'll roll for an initiative, too. Fine.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay, so then.
Kostadis Roussos: skeleton.
Nikhil: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: Mela goes, oh, these are undead!
Kostadis Roussos: Undead are a, a kind of monster in Dungeons & Dragons that has,
Nikhil: Whitewater standing.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, you wanna, they, you can say that. All right, okay, and so we need Sister Mela.
Kostadis Roussos: She's got a 15.
Nikhil: Can we not quickly run through the door?
Nikhil: Back to bed, though.
Kostadis Roussos: Many things can happen, but we're going to stop here.
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: You didn't have to do this.
Kostadis Roussos: I didn't have, I don't have to do many.
Nikhil: No, I would say, like, this is probably the best part of all the, you know, games played so far.
Kostadis Roussos: But.
Nikhil: Right.
Nikhil: No, I mean, like, of all the sessions that we played.
Nikhil: Best cliffhanger or, you know, the best,
Kostadis Roussos: Cliffhanger.
Nikhil: cliffhanger or the story progression.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you know, this is the story, the state, you know, stories have to, it takes a little bit of time for stories to move. Okay, so, turn.
Kostadis Roussos: all right okay we will stop here for and we'll stop here because it's almost nine o'clock all right.
Nikhil: Okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Great. It was great hanging with you. It was great hanging with you, man.
Nikhil: Likewise, I missed playing with you last week.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Just compensated for, like, the last two weeks, I guess.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, yes it did. Alright man, take care, have a good one.
Nikhil: See you, bye.
Kostadis Roussos: Bye bye.